pagestudy.com 2015-06-11

# Privacy Policy - Pagestudy

The Pagestudy.com ("Pagestudy") Privacy Policy covers Pagestudy's treatment of personal or personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that may be collected when you are on the Pagestudy web site and when you use Pagestudy's services. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Pagestudy does not own or control, or to individuals that are not under Pagestudy's supervisory control.

#### Collection and Use of Personal Information.

Pagestudy may collect Personal Information when you use certain services on the Pagestudy web site or when you visit cookie-enabled web pages. Pagestudy may also log your IP address when you use the Pagestudy web site. Pagestudy uses this Personal Information to fulfill requests for our services or products, to contact users regarding changes to our site or our business, and to customize the content that you might see on the Pagestudy web site. Pagestudy may also use "cookie" files to better serve your needs by creating a customized web site which fits your needs.

#### Sharing and Disclosure of Personal Information.

Pagestudy will not sell or rent your Personal Information to any individual, business, or government entity. Pagestudy will share your Personal Information ith other entities should you request Pagestudy to share such information, or if Pagestudy is required to respond to court orders, subpoenas or other legal process.

#### User Accounts.

You have the ability to edit your User Information at any time, and may delete your account at your convenience. Under no condition will Pagestudy share your user account information with another individual, business or government entity, unless Pagestudy is required to respond to court orders, subpoenas or other legal process. Pagestudy allows users to set up accounts to update information on web domains, such updates are public.

#### Content rating and parental controls.

Pagestudy.com does not offer any content or services for use by children. If you are under 18, parent or guardian is required to supervise your use of Pagestudy.com.

#### Encryption.

Pagestudy uses all economically reasonable security measures in protecting user data. All user account pages are protected with Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") encryption. All user accounts must be accessed with usernames and passwords. You are advised not to share your username and password with any other person.

#### Amendments.

Pagestudy reserves the right to amend this policy at any time. Pagestudy will contact registered users by e-mail, and shall also post a notice of changes on its web site, when and if the terms of this policy are amended.

#### Contact.

You may contact Pagestudy directly by e-mailing Pagestudy Contact Email should you have any questions regarding this policy.

#### Report a policy violation

You can report a policy violation using [this form](http://pagestudy.com/report/).
